petango.com 2015-09-05

# Privacy Policy

####### Pethealth Inc. and Petango.com Privacy Statement 

This privacy policy applies in respect of the websites controlled by Pethealth Inc. and/or its subsidiary and other affiliated entities ("Pethealth," "we" or "us") where this privacy policy is posted under the authority of Pethealth (collectively, the "Sites"), as well as, unless otherwise indicated, in respect of any other personal information collected by Pethealth. **BY USING THE SITES, YOU CONSENT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND TO OUR PROCESSING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION FOR THE PURPOSES STATED BELOW. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITES.**

### A. Information Collected

We collect two types of information from users of the Sites: **(1) Personally Identifiable Information;** and **(2) Non-Personally Identifiable Information, such as your IP address or cookies-related information.**

For the purposes of this Policy, users of the Sites include Guests and Members. Guests to the Sites are able to browse the Sites, search profiles, and view various content on the Sites, such as articles or polls, without entering any personal information. In respect of Guests, only certain non-personally identifiable information is collected. In respect of Members, certain personally identifiable information is collected when Members create a Member account, enter into a sweepstakes/contest, purchase a product from The Petango Store and certain other occasions as may arise in connection with their use of the Sites. In addition, as in the case of a Guest, non-personally identifiable information is captured automatically and may or may not be linked to the personally identifiable information of the Member in question.

### (1) Personally Identifiable Information

**Personally identifiable information may include, but is not necessarily limited to, a Member's:**

  1. Name
  2. Location
  3. Email address
  4. Age
  5. Gender
  6. Credit Card information
  7. Billing Address

Members of the Site may also provide, in exchange for greater access to features and functionality and/or to receive the full experience of Membership, certain otherwise non-personally identifiable information such as income, age, gender, pictures and opinions that may be linked to personally identifiable information that you voluntarily provide to us. 

**If you do not want Pethealth to collect your personally identifiable information, please do not provide it to us. To learn how to limit our use of the information you provide to us, see below at Section F.**

### (2) Non-Personally Identifiable Information

"Non-Personally Identifiable Information" can be technical information, such as your browser type, IP address, screen resolution, Internet connection speed, operating system, the date and time of you access our Sites, the web pages you visit and the Internet address of the web site from which you linked to our site. It could also be demographic information, such as your age, gender or interests. Non-personally identifiable information does NOT identify you personally. Here are some examples of the non-personally identifiable information that is collected via the Sites and a description of how this information may be used: 

  * Internet Protocol (IP) address -- Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data -- such as the web pages you view. We use this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to tailor our Sites to the interests of our users and to measure traffic within our Sites. 
  * Your Activity on the Sites – _Cookies:_ A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used to collect information about your activity on the Sites. For example, when someone visits a page within the Sites, a cookie is placed on the user's machine (if the user accepts cookies) or is read if the user has visited the Sites previously. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but if you do, you may not be able to take advantage of the personalized features enjoyed by other users to our Sites. _Web Beacons_ _(also known as "clear gifs," "web bugs" or "pixel tags"):_ "Web Beacons" are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to allow us to count users who have visited certain pages of the Sites and to help determine the effectiveness of promotional or advertising campaigns. When used in HTML-formatted email messages, web beacons can tell the sender whether and when the email has been opened. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on web pages. 
  * Demographic Information -- "Demographic Information" includes your gender, age, zip code and interests, which you voluntarily provide to us on the Sites. We use this information to provide you with personalized services and to analyze trends to ensure the information provided by the Sites meets your needs.
  * Aggregated Information -- Please note that we also consider aggregated information that does not correspond to any one person to be non-personally identifiable information.

### B. Use of Information Collected Via the Sites

**(1) Personally Identifiable Information.**

We use your personally identifiable information for the following purposes:

  * To deliver services, such as educational programs, information, newsletters, pet insurance or pet related products, you request or purchase; 
  * To alert you to special offers, updated information and other new services from Pethealth, or other third parties, or to forward promotional materials; 
  * To complete a transaction or service requested by you; 
  * To fulfill the terms of a promotion; 
  * To assist in ensuring the Sites are relevant to your needs; 
  * To help us create and publish content most relevant to you; 
  * To notify you about a material change to this privacy policy or the Visitor Agreement, if necessary; 
  * To allow you access to limited-entry areas of the Sites; and 
  * To contact you in response to sign up forms such as Contact Us or Order Inquiry. 

We do not use your personally identifiable information for purposes other than those to which you consent and your personally identifiable information is deleted when consent is withdrawn or when the purposes in question have been met.

**(2) Non-Personally Identifiable Information.**

We use non-personally identifiable information collected on the Sites in the manner disclosed above at Section A (2).

### C. Sharing and Disclosure of Information

**(1) Personally Identifiable Information**

We may share or disclose your personally identifiable information in the instances set out below, subject to the "Opt-Out" options described further below at Section F: 

(i) To unaffiliated third-party service providers, agents or independent contractors for the purposes of fulfilling a service to you. For example, if you submit or monitor a claim or wish to utilize social networking functionality in connection with one of the Sites, we may disclose your personally identifiable information to certain trusted third-party service providers and/or agents to assist in the fulfillment of the service(s) in question. As well, if you choose to watch an educational program on the Sites, we may share your personally identifiable information with third-parties as required in order to provide the program to you. In addition, if you email us a question, we may use your email address to process your request and respond to your question. Also, if you are entering a sweepstakes or contest, we may use your personally identifiable information in order to fulfill the terms of that promotion. This means that we may share the information for prize fulfillment purposes or mail carriers. We also may share your information with the co-sponsor of that promotion. In the case of such sweepstakes/contests/promotions, we will share your information only in accordance with the consent you provide us for such purposes.

(ii) To unaffiliated third-party service providers, agents or independent contractors who help us maintain our Sites and provide other administrative services to us (including, but not limited to, order processing and fulfillment, providing customer service, maintaining and analyzing data, sending customer communications on Pethealth's behalf, and entry collection, winner selection and prize fulfillment for contests, sweepstakes and other promotions). We seek to ensure that these unaffiliated third parties will not use the personally identifiable information for any other purpose than to provide the administrative services for which they are responsible. Because such unaffiliated third-party service providers that help us administer our Sites will have access to users' personally identifiable information, if you do not wish for our unaffiliated third-party service providers to have access to your information, please do not register or submit any personally identifiable information to us. 

(iii) To complete your purchase. If you choose to make a purchase on the Sites, we may collect from you your credit card number, billing address and other information related to such purchase, and we may use such collected information in order to fulfill your purchase. We may also provide such information, or other personally identifiable information provided by you, to unaffiliated third parties as necessary to complete your purchase (for example, to process your credit card). 

(iv) To comply with the law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the requirements of law or comply with legal process served on us, protect and defend our rights or property, including the rights and property of Pethealth and its family of Sites or act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of our end users. 

(v) To third parties as part of any corporate reorganization process including, but not limited to, mergers, acquisitions, and sales of all or substantially all of our assets. 

(vi) To track and analyze usage and volume statistical information and provide such information to third parties. 

(vii) To protect against potential fraud, we may verify with third parties the information collected from these Sites. In the course of such verification, we may receive personally identifiable information about you from such services. In particular, if you use a credit card or debit card to purchase services with us, we may use card authorization and fraud screening services to verify that your card information and address matches the information that you supplied to us, and that the card has not been reported as lost or stolen. 

Except as described in this Privacy Policy or at the time we request the information, we do not share or otherwise disclose your personally identifiable information to any third parties. 

**(2) Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

We may share this non-personal information with third parties.

### D. Age Screening and the Collection and Use of Information from Children

No one under the age of 18 years is permitted to become a Member of a Site and we will not knowingly allow anyone under the age of 18 years to register as a Member of a Site or make a purchase. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from a user under the age of 18 years, we will delete the information from our records as soon as we discover it.

### E. International Transfer of Information

If you choose to provide us with personally identifiable information, Pethealth may transfer that information to its affiliates and subsidiaries or to other third parties, across borders, and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring your personally identifiable information to the United States which does not have the same data protection laws as the EU and by providing your personally identifiable information you consent to: 

  * the use of your personally identifiable information for the uses identified above in accordance with this privacy policy; and 
  * the transfer of your personally identifiable information to the United States as indicated above. 

### F. Opt-Out

We communicate with users who subscribe to our services on a regular basis via email. For example, we may use your email address to confirm your request, to send you notice of payments, to send you information about changes to our products and services, and to send notices and other disclosures as required by law. Generally, users cannot opt-out of these communications, but they will be primarily informational in nature rather than promotional. 

However, we provide you the opportunity to exercise an opt-out choice if you do not want to receive other types of communication from us, such as emails or updates from us regarding new services and products offered on this Site or if you do not want us to share your personally identifiable information with third parties. The opt-out choice may be exercised by ticking or un-ticking the appropriate box if such checkbox is available at the points where personally identifiable information is collected or by contacting us (see below at Section N). We will process your unsubscribe request as soon as possible, but please be aware that in some circumstances you may receive a few more messages until the unsubscribe is processed. You also may opt-out of receiving such emails by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link within the text of the email.

### G. Forums, Chat Rooms and Other Public Posting Areas

Please note that any information you include in a message you post to any chat room, forum or other public posting area is available to anyone with Internet access. If you don't want people to know your e-mail address, for example, don't include it in any message you post publicly. PLEASE BE EXTREMELY CAREFUL WHEN DISCLOSING ANY INFORMATION IN CHAT ROOMS, FORUMS AND OTHER PUBLIC POSTING AREAS. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE USE BY OTHERS OF THE INFORMATION THAT YOU DISCLOSE IN CHAT ROOMS, FORUMS AND OTHER PUBLIC POSTING AREAS.

### H. Third Party Web Sites

This statement applies solely to information collected on the Sites. The Sites may contain links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other web sites. You should consult the privacy policies of other sites to learn how your privacy is protected when you visit those sites.

### I. Third Party Advertisers

We may use advertisers, third party ad networks, and other advertising companies, to serve advertisements on the Sites. Please be advised that such advertising companies may gather information about your visit to the Sites or other sites (such as through cookies, web beacons and other technologies) to enable such advertising companies to market products or services to you, to monitor which ads have been served to your browser and which web pages you were viewing when such ads were delivered. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices please _click here_. **PLEASE NOTE THAT THIS POLICY DOES NOT COVER THE COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION BY SUCH ADVERTISING COMPANIES.**

### J. Accessing Your Personally Identifiable Information and Privacy Preferences

We provide you with an opportunity to access your personally identifiable information to ensure it is correct, accurate and current. To edit your personally identifiable information, please log in at the Site in question and access your account. To be removed from a mailing list or if you would prefer that we do not share your information with third party marketers, please make sure to indicate that on the relevant Site registration form. If for any reason you are not able to update or edit your personally identifiable information through a Site, you can access such information by contacting us as described below at Section N. We will make reasonable efforts to accommodate your request.

### K. Assignment

In the event that all or part of our assets or sold or acquired by another party, or in the event of a merger, you agree to grant us the right to assign the personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information collected via the Sites.

### L. Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy from time to time. When we do, we will also revise the "last update" date at the bottom of this privacy policy. For changes to this privacy policy that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of personal information you have provided to us, we will attempt to notify you via email and obtain your consent before implementing the change by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account and/or by placing a prominent notice on the Sites.

### M. Security

No data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.  
Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure security on our systems. We use firewalls to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction, and maintain appropriate physical, electronic and administrative safeguards to protect the data. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software.

### N. Contacting Pethealth

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our privacy practices, please contact the Pethealth Privacy Officer at:  
Privacy@pethealthinc.com.  
You may also contact us via letter-mail at:

Pethealth Inc.  
710 Dorval Drive,  
Suite 400  
Oakville, Ontario, Canada  
L6K 3V7  
Attn: Pethealth Privacy Officer  
**1-866-600-2449  
**Email: privacy@pethealthinc.com 

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding Pethealth Inc.'s disclosure of personally identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us: 

Pethealth Inc.  
710 Dorval Drive,  
Suite 400  
Oakville, Ontario, Canada  
L6K 3V7  
**1-866-600-2449  
**Email: privacy@pethealthinc.com
